Kirito,
Yuna, Kirito, Yuna,
Kirito, Mali, Mali, Kirito,
Vorumb, Tree, Kirito, Tree, Kirito,
Yuna, Kirito, Tree, Kirito,
Zipo, Suguha, Yuna, Kirito, Yuna,
Kirito, confirmation.
It's been almost two years
since this game of death began.
I'm still going it alone.
fighting solo on the front lines.
Akihiko Kayaba's out
there somewhere, watching.
I wonder what he's thinking right now.
Guess I'll head home.
c L .
I don't know what I'm saying,
but I don't know what I'm saying,
but I don't know what I'm saying.
I'm afraid of the back of the back of
my back, but I'm still in the moment.
I've been looking for a long time,
and I've been looking for a long time.
Here is my heart,
and I've been looking
for a long time.
I wanna know what we do, I'll
give you everything I have
You've got to be kidding.
No way.
This is an Skills rare item.
Holy crap, this is the first
time I've ever seen one.
Hey, Kirito, don't you already
have all the money you need?
I'll buy it, but I'm saying, wouldn't
you rather have it for dinner?
Sure, it's just, well, who knows
if I'll ever get another one.
So keep it.
What's the point?
Look, to prepare an item like this, you
need to have a high enough cooking skill.
Yeah, you're right.
If we try, we just burn it.
Kirito.
I've got my chef.
Uh, what chef?
Hey, Asuna's here.
Seeing you in a dump like
this is beyond weird.
Oh, save it.
I came to see if you were still alive.
You know, it's almost time
for the next boss raid.
I'm on your friend list.
If you want to know I'm
alive, just check that.
Whatever, now I know you're alive.
Anyway, what are you up to?
What's all this about a chef?
Oh, yeah, that.
I was wondering what your
cooking skill level is.
Hmm.
Totally maxed it out last week. What?
Cool, huh?
Well, if you're that
good, I need a favor. Hmm?
You got a Rika rabbit? I'll trade you.
All you have to do is cook it up for
me, and I'll let you have a little bite.
Half. Deal?
Yeah, deal.
All right!
Sorry, pal.
You heard the lady.
Guess I'm keeping it.
Yeah, but you could at least
let me taste it, right?
I thought we were tight, man.
I'll write a review for
you, but only two pages.
Promise.
Damn, that is cold.
So, where am I going to cook it?
Oh, well...
I'm guessing not your place, right?
You even own any cookware? Mama.
Okay,
because the main ingredient is special,
I won't have a problem if
we used my place this time.
Thank you for escorting me.
You may go.
I'm sorry, ma 'am, but I can't allow you
to go home with such a shady character.
I don't know the extent of his shadiness,
But I know he's quite skilled.
In fact, he's ten levels
above you, Kuradeel.
Are you implying I'm inferior to him?
Oh, I know.
He's one of those beaters, isn't he?
Yeah.
What if I am?
You shouldn't go with him, ma 'am.
All him and his kind care
about are themselves.
You can't expect anything good
to come from scum like that.
Hey, what's going on?
That's Lightning Flash Asuna.
You're right.
She's really cute.
Listen, I'm second-in-command here.
I am ordering you to go home.
Are you sure about this?
Of course!
Whoa.
There's hardly anyone around.
It's really cool.
If you like it so much,
why don't you move here?
I don't know, this floor seems
way out of my price range.
Anyway, what's the deal
with that guy back there?
He was mad-dogging me like crazy.
Oh, he's just my bodyguard.
The guild's new policy says all
higher-ups have to have an escort.
It's lame.
The guild didn't have all these
rules and regulations before.
We used to be really small.
But then, more and more people joined up.
After that, when we became the strongest
guild, everything started getting weird.
Well, I'm probably making a
bigger deal out of it than it is.
Anyway, we better hurry.
It's getting dark.
Oh, okay.
Wow, you've got a killer pad.
Hey, how much did all this cost?
The room and the furniture
cost around $4 million coal.
Anyway, make yourself at home.
Uh, sure.
Holy moly.
Four million.
Man, that's a lot of coal.
I'm sure I've earned that much,
too, but blowing it all on a flat?
Are you going to take
off your coat or what?
Oh, yeah, sorry.
So this is a legendary Skills ingredient.
Okay, how do you want this cooked up?
I thought I'd leave that
decision up to the chef.
In that case, how about
we make it into a stew?
Rika, that's pretty much
the definition of a stew.
In real life, there'd be a lot more
steps involved in preparing this.
Cooking an SAO is so simple.
Believe it or not, it's kind of boring.
That takes care of that.
Now for the next step.
I was thinking about making
a couple side dishes.
I've been here two years, and this is the
first time I've ever eaten Skills food.
I'm so happy I survived
long enough to eat that.
Yeah, me too.
It's so weird.
Sometimes, I don't know,
I get this feeling that like
I've lived here my entire life.
You ever feel like that?
Yeah, almost all the time.
In fact, there's days I don't even
think about the real world at all.
And it's not just me.
These days,
more and more people
don't seem to care about
clearing the game and getting
back to the real world.
I notice there's not that many players
out there fighting on the front lines.
Maybe 500, if that.
I guess they're used to it.
They don't care anymore.
Yeah, well, I want to go back.
I mean, there's things I haven't done yet.
I have to.
I know how you feel.
And when you stop to consider
it, there's everyone else, right?
All the people who still count on us?
If we give up, it's not fair to them.
Uh-uh, don't go there.
What?
I've seen that same look
on guys' faces before,
and always right before
they proposed to me.
You should see your face.
I guess you never had a girlfriend before.
Eh, whatever, I'm a solo player.
And you're okay with that?
You don't ever want to join a guild?
I know how the beta players
don't fit in with the guilds.
But ever since we got to Floor 70,
things are getting more dangerous.
The monster algorithms
are even more irregular.
There are things a solo
player can't handle.
Unexpected things.
Sometimes warping out isn't an option.
Yeah, well, I'm pretty careful.
I work better by myself anyway.
Besides, most of the time, instead of
helping, party members just get in the way.
Oh, yeah?
My bad.
Everyone except for you. Good.
So, what do you say you
and me team up again?
Black's my lucky color this week anyway.
Hold up a sec.
Don't you have stuff you
have to do for your guild?
You can't just bail on him.
It's not like we have any
leveling quotas to meet.
Well then, what about your bodyguard?
I'll just ditch him.
The front lines are dangerous, though.
Okay, fine.
Well, I suppose thanks are in
order for the meal, so thank you.
Thank you for cooking it.
Maybe next time.
What am I saying?
I'll never get my hands on
something like that again.
No way.
You can make anything yummy if
you have the skills to cook.
Looking at this world and seeing
what it's become since we got here,
Is this really what Akihiko
Kayaba wanted to create?
Where is she?
What is this thing?
Hmm, squishy.
Ow.
Um, hey.
Good morning, Asuna.
What's wrong?
Why are you behaving like this, ma 'am?
I'm only following orders.
Please, let's go back to headquarters.
I won't, especially not with you.
And why were you lurking around
my house in the morning, huh?
You have a bad habit of
leaving without any warning.
So for the past month,
part of my mission has been to
keep an eye on you in Selmburg.
What?
Who ordered this?
It wasn't the commander.
With all due respect, ma 'am,
my mission is to guard you,
no matter where you are,
including your home.
No, it doesn't, you idiot!
I wish you would be a little more
understanding about this, ma 'am.
Now then, let's return to headquarters.
Sorry, but I'll be borrowing your
second-in-command for the day,
so you'll just have to
make do without her.
I'll take responsibility for her security.
Don't worry, it's not like
we're going on a boss raid.
You can go.
She'll be fine with me.
Insolent punk!
Do you know who I am?
I'm a member of the glorious
Knights of the Blood Oath.
A low-level player like
you couldn't protect her.
I can do a better job of it than you.
You've got a big mouth, kid.
So I'm going to give you a chance to
prove just how tough you really are.
Are you sure? Don't worry.
I'll tell the commander how this happened.
Please move to a safe distance, ma 'am.
I'm going to prove beyond any doubt that
I am the only one who can protect you.
Kirito's gonna duel a guy from
the Knights of the Blood Oath.
This will be fun to watch.
I can't believe it!
Holy crap, he destroyed his sword.
How did he do that?
If you want to try again with another
weapon, I'll be glad to take you on.
Or we can call it a day.
Asuna!
I don't know how, but he cheated!
You saw how he destroyed my sword!
He must have used some kind of trick!
There's no other way I could have
lost to a pathetic beater like him!
Kuradeel,
as second-in-command of the
Knights of the Blood Oath,
I'm relieving you of your
duties as my bodyguard.
You're to return to headquarters
and wait for further orders.
You can't be serious!
Damn you!
Teleport.
Ransom.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to drag you into that.
No, it's no big deal.
I'm worried about you. Are you okay?
Yeah, I am.
The guild's getting on my nerves is all.
Maybe because I've been so
focused on clearing the game.
Or maybe because I'm so demanding
of the other members in the guild.
Yeah, I get that.
But you didn't have much of a choice.
Think about it.
If you'd done things any different,
you think your guild would have
gotten as far as they have?
I mean, what do I know?
I just mess around as
a solo player, right?
The thing is, if you take a day off to
team up with a loser like me, so what?
That's your decision to make.
In my opinion, no one's
got the right to complain.
Screw him.
Wow, thank you for your
opinion on the subject.
Okay, I accept your offer and I'll
be taking a day off from the guild.
You can play forward today.
Huh?
Wait a second, aren't we supposed
to take turns as forward?
Sorry, it's my day off, remember?
Oh, come on!
Having someone along who knows how
to fight sure makes things easier.
Switch with me, Kirito!
Yeah, right!
Kirito, look.
Is that what I think it is?
Uh-huh.
We found the boss room.
What do we do?
You think we should look inside?
Well, we came all this way.
Besides, boss monsters never
leave the rooms they guard.
I think we'll be okay
if we just take a peek.
Oh, okay.
Have a teleport crystal
ready, just in case.
Right.
Okay, are you ready? Mm-hmm.
I don't know.
I'll be on, I'll be on.
I heard the sound of the sound?
It's a little sad to me. Yeah,
yeah, yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
I can't believe this love.
In the front of my eyes,
I can't believe it.
Even if I'm dreaming, I can't believe it.
I'm still in the middle of my heart.
Next time, the blue-eyed demon.